

Contacts

(t) +94 70 1182171

ttheruwandi@gmail.com

in Linkedin

@ Github

Portfolio

293/4, Pahala Yagoda, Ganemulla.

Personal Info

Date of Birth : 12 Dec 2000

Gender : Female

Nationality : Sri Lankan

Languages : English, Sinhala

REFERENCES

Dr. Yohan Pandigama Founder-C2L3 Lecture(CS) -Sri Lanka Technological Campus, Padukka. Fomer HoD-IT - CINEC Campus,

Malabe. MIEEE, MIEEE-CS, MACM, MBCS, MSC(SL), MSC, BIT 0713008883

yohanp@sltc.ac.lk

Dr. Dileepa Fernando Post doctoral Research Fellow- HP-NTU Corporate Lab, Singapore.

dileepa.fernando@ntu.edu.sg

THARUSHI HERATH

SE - Quality Assurance

I am an Associate QA professional with over a year of experience, dedicated to ensuring product excellence and customer satisfaction. I have a keen eye for detail and am committed to continuous improvement. I collaborate effectively with teams and have proficiency in industry-standard QA tools and methodologies.

Work Experience

Oct 2023 - Present

Logiccodex Solutions PVT (Ltd)

Part Time - Project Coordinator Nov 2023 - Present

Logiccodex Solutions PVT (Ltd)

Intern Software Engineer - Quality Assurance Aug 2023 - Feb 2024

SLT Telecom

Education

O B.Sc (Hons) in Information Technology specialized in Software

Engineering

SLTC Research University 2020 - 2024

GCE Advanced Level - Technology Stream

Rathnavali Balika Vidyalaya, Gampaha 2019

Skills

- Software testing (Selenium, Postman)
- Programing (HTML, CSS, SQL basic, React.js)
- Project management & Coordinator
- Content creating
- Photo editing (Adobe Photoshop)

Courses

- Web programming course in FTGE Campus.
- Foundation of user experience (UX) design course in Coursera.
- Cyber security course in CYBERHAT 1.0 online workshop.
- Cloud computing application, part 1: cloud system and infrastructure in Coursera.